<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Boone Hall Fright Nights</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome To Boone Hall Fright Nights!</string>
    <string name="part_intro">All actor positions</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="safety">Safety</string>
    <string name="more_to_come">There was a lot i wanted to do with this. However time waits for no man.\n
        I wanted to add something for the hayride Narrators on the hayride.\n
        I also wanted to add more on safety.\n
        Makeup designs will also be added in the future.\n
        All things considered I don\'t think i did ok for a guy who only knows how to add a textview.</string>
    <string name="empty">place stuff here</string>
    <string name="error_text">Small error.\n
    1.You might not have the TV changed.\n
    2.You need to stop clicking stuff that might be broken. </string>
    
    <string name="part_section_title">TITLE HERE</string>
    <string name="part_section_1">INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="part_section_2">MAKEUP</string>
    <string name="part_section_3">SAFETY</string>
   
    <string name="info_req">INFO</string>
    <string name="makeup_req">MAKEUP</string>
    <string name="safety_req">SAFETY</string>
    
    <string name="AN_title_1">Welcome Amy</string>
    <string name="AN_title_2">Clown #1</string>
    <string name="AN_title_3">Drop Window Clown</string>
    <string name="AN_title_4">Toy Box Clown #1</string>
    <string name="AN_title_5">Toy Box Clown #2</string>
    <string name="AN_title_6">Drop Box Clown</string>
    <string name="AN_title_7">Bedroom Amy</string>
    <string name="AN_title_8">Bathroom Clown</string>
    
   <string name="AN_info_1">You will need to rely on jump scares.
       You will need to take advantage of blending into the 3D room.
       Doing this will be easy, just sit back and look at the door,
       when people come in wait until the door closes then jump up.\n 
       SCREEMS OF TERROR MURDER AND PHYSCO will be needed.\n
       Possible lines might be:\n
       Want to play?\n 
       Welcome to my nightmare\n
       Take full advantage of the ones that scream the most. </string>
       
   <string name="AN_info_2"> You will be standing inside a walk-in closet.
       Just walk or jump out with your knife in hand and look at people. Make 
       jerking motions that will confuse the people, once confused find the one that 
       HATES clowns. Do not follow too far, allow the people to get out of your 
       area. No speaking rolls will be needed, HOWEVER you can scream at them. </string>
   
   <string name="AN_info_3">You will have a peek hole that you will need to use to see
       your targets. Click the lever above you to drop the window. Jump out and scream.
       It isn\'t necessary to talk but do so if you find something creepy to say.</string>
       
   <string name="AN_info_4">You can pop up out of the box or walk for behind the box.
       Try to target the middle of the group for max effect. No dialog is needed but 
       if you can find something creepy to say then go for it. Work with the second guy in 
       the room to increase the scare factor.  </string>
       
   <string name="AN_info_5">You can pop up out of the box or walk for behind the box.
       Try to target the middle of the group for max effect. No dialog is needed but 
       if you can find something creepy to say then go for it. Work with the second guy in 
       the room to increase the scare factor. </string>
       
   <string name="AN_info_6">You will have a peek hole that you will need to use to see
       your targets. Click the lever above you to drop the window. Jump out and scream.
       It isn\'t necessary to talk but do so if you find something creepy to say. </string>
       
   <string name="AN_info_7"> Amy has gotten older. Oh what fun, Use the bed to your advantage.
       You can move the bed by shifting your weight. Act like your nightmares are possessing you.\n
       You will need to scream and shout at your victims.\n 
       Some lines should include.\n 
       "'Get out!'"\n
       "'Why do you want to hurt me.'"\n 
       Be creative.</string>
       
   <string name="AN_info_8">End of the line? Use the shower curtain to your advantage. You can 
       also use the blow up wall to hide, just make sure to walk out with enough time to get them by you. 
       </string>
       
   <string name="AN_makeup_1"> You will need whiteface and blacked out eyes.\n
       You will not need tons of blood but a small splatter effect will work. </string> 
   <string name="AN_makeup_2"> You will only need eye makeup. </string>
   <string name="AN_makeup_3"> You will only need eye makeup. </string>
   <string name="AN_makeup_4"> You will only need eye makeup. </string>
   <string name="AN_makeup_5"> You will only need eye makeup. </string>
   <string name="AN_makeup_6"> You will only need eye makeup. </string>
   <string name="AN_makeup_7"> You will need whiteface and blacked out eyes.\n
       You will not need tons of blood but a small splatter effect will work. </string>
   <string name="AN_makeup_8"> You will only need eye makeup. </string>
   
   <string name="AN_safety_1"> DO NOT GET TOO CLOSE!\n
       If you see drunk or unsafe people do not go near them.\n
       Watch your step, toys and objects are on the floor. </string>
  <string name="AN_safety_2"> DO NOT GET TOO CLOSE!\n
       If you see drunk or unsafe people do not go near them.\n
       Watch your step the mask will limit your vision. </string>
  <string name="AN_safety_3"> DO NOT GET TOO CLOSE!\n
       If you see drunk or unsafe people do not go near them.\n
       Control how far you pop out of the box. </string>
  <string name="AN_safety_4">DO NOT GET TOO CLOSE!\n
       If you see drunk or unsafe people do not go near them.\n
       Control how far you pop out of the box.</string>
  <string name="AN_safety_5">DO NOT GET TOO CLOSE!\n
       If you see drunk or unsafe people do not go near them.\n</string>
  <string name="AN_safety_6">DO NOT GET TOO CLOSE!\n
       If you see drunk or unsafe people do not go near them.\n
       Control how far you pop out of the box.</string>
  <string name="AN_safety_7">DO NOT GET TOO CLOSE!\n
       If you see drunk or unsafe people do not go near them.\n
       Do not jump off the bed, it is unstable and can\'t be used that way.</string>
  <string name="AN_safety_8">DO NOT GET TOO CLOSE!\n
       If you see drunk or unsafe people do not go near them.\n
       Watch your step the mask will limit your vision.</string>
       
  <string name="CM_title_1">Welcome Host</string>
  <string name="CM_title_2">Line Divider</string>
  <string name="CM_title_3">Drop Window 1</string>
  <string name="CM_title_4">Gargoyle</string>
  <string name="CM_title_5">Arch Hall Statue</string>
  <string name="CM_title_6">Iron Smith</string>
  <string name="CM_title_7">Hooping Creature</string>
  <string name="CM_title_8">Kitchen Hag</string>
  <string name="CM_title_9">Beast Operator</string>
  <string name="CM_title_10">Torture Cell Victim</string>
  <string name="CM_title_11">Stretch door</string>
  <string name="CM_title_12">Executioner Room</string>
  <string name="CM_title_13">Drop Window 2</string>
  <string name="CM_title_14">Overhead Creature</string>
  <string name="CM_title_15">Impailer Keeper</string>
  <string name="CM_title_16">Demon Druid 1</string>
  <string name="CM_title_17">Demon Druid 2</string>
  <string name="CM_title_18">Chainsaw 1</string>
  <string name="CM_title_19">Chainsaw 2</string>
  
  <string name="CM_info_1">Your job is to welcome the people into the nightmare that is about to come.\n
      You will need to lead them into the center of the room and activate the video discreetly. \n
      A lot of dialog is needed, use lines that welcome people to their doom.\n 
      Remind them of no pushing. And that they will all die later.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_2">Your job is to line divide people. Do not allow the entire group of people to 
      go through all at once. This is to allow the other actors to get back in place after each group.\n 
      Be creative on your dialog. Jump scare people with the blacked out wall. </string>
  <string name="CM_info_3">you will have a peek hole that you will need to use to see
       your targets. Click the lever above you to drop the window. Jump out and scream.
       It isn\'t necessary to talk but do so if you find something creepy to say</string>
  <string name="CM_info_4">Stay perfectly still. Your job is to become perfectly still as a statue. 
      When the device does its show, jerk your head and jump at them.\n 
      No dialog is needed.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_5">You will look just like the statues in the hall. Wait until the people get close and 
      then scream at them.\n
      You can use dialog if you want to, just make it creepy.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_6">You will have a large metal object that you can bang against the desk. You are the 
      keeper of death. Act like you enjoy causing them pain and suffering. 
      Dialog is needed, such as:\n
      ANOTHER DEAD MAN WALKING\n
      READY TO DIE TONIGHT\n
      Be creative in your dialog and actions.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_7">You are equipped with a special device called a sky hook. Jump out from the curtain 
      and attack. The sky hook will pull u back into place using the spring attached to it. \n
      WARNING: DO NOT ATTACH OR DEATTACH ANYTHING ON THIS DEVICE. RISK OF SERIOUS INJURY OR DEATH CAN OCCURE 
      IF YOU MESS WITH IT. IT IS SET UP FOR YOUR SAFTY, DO NOT DO ANYTHING TO CHANGE THAT! </string>
  <string name="CM_info_8">As they enter your kitchen scream at them, your goal is to become an old witch like
      lady that wants to eat their soul. \n
      Use dialog like:\n
      FRESH VICTIMS\n
      STAY FOR DINNER LITTLE ONES\n
      Laugh a little bit in a creepy way.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_9">Activate the beast by using the buttons on the controls. Then push out the beat by leaning 
      forward. Just make sure not to step out where people can see you. Pull by the beast by leaning back.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_10">Scream terror and mayhem. Jump up and down and ask them to let you out. You are about to 
      die and are left in there until they kill you. Act like a madman.\n
      Dialog should be along the lines of:\n
      HELP ME!\n
      LET ME OUT OF HERE\n
      Be creative on your dialog and actions.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_11">You will be able to see an outline of your targets through the door. Place your hands 
      on the spandex door and push out. Do not touch them but target the ones who are not paying attrition. </string>
  <string name="CM_info_12">Bang against the rack in the room. Jump out of the darkness with shouts of anger and hate.
      This will require dialog like: \n
      YOU WILL DIE HERE LIKE HIM!\n
      FRESH MEAT FOR THE GRINDER!\n
      Feel free to be creative.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_13">you will have a peek hole that you will need to use to see
       your targets. Click the lever above you to drop the window. Jump out and scream.
       It isn\'t necessary to talk but do so if you find something creepy to say</string>
  <string name="CM_info_14">Lay down on top of a board and reach down at people.\n
      No dialog is needed.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_15">Your job is to distract them as the spikes impailer them. Scream and shout at them in 
      anger and rage. \n
      Create your own dialog, be creative.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_16">The spitter and other demons activate off of IR sensors. Jump out at your targets 
      screaming and shouting. \n
      Create your own dialog, be creative.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_17">Last room of the house, hide in the middle of the statues and wait until they are distracted 
      then attack them. Scream, shout, yell, and ask them to join the dark lord.\n
      Be creative on your dialog.</string>
  <string name="CM_info_18">Work with your partner at the time and attack them customers that pass your area.\n 
      WARNING: ALTHOUGH FUNNEY AS HELL. DO NOT CHASE THE CUSTOMERS FROM ANY ATTRACTIONS INTO THE DITCH. THIS CAN 
      CAUSE SERIOUS INJURY TO YOU AND THE CUSTOMER. </string>
  <string name="CM_info_19">Work with your partner at the time and attack them customers that pass your area.\n 
      WARNING: ALTHOUGH FUNNEY AS HELL. DO NOT CHASE THE CUSTOMERS FROM ANY ATTRACTIONS INTO THE DITCH. THIS CAN 
      CAUSE SERIOUS INJURY TO YOU AND THE CUSTOMER.</string>
  
  <string name="HH_title_1">Ma at Ma\'s Diener</string>
  <string name="HH_title_2">Pa at Ma\'s Diener</string>
  <string name="HH_title_3">Daughter w/ Chainsaw</string>
  <string name="HH_title_4">T-Rex operator</string>
  <string name="HH_title_5">Gilly #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_6">Gilly #2</string>
  <string name="HH_title_7">Electric Shed Worker</string>
  <string name="HH_title_8">Scissor Serpent Ghoul #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_9">Scissor Serpent Ghoul #2</string>
  <string name="HH_title_10">Dragon Ghoul #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_11">Dragon Ghoul #2</string>
  <string name="HH_title_12">Gravedigger</string>
  <string name="HH_title_13">Graveyard Drop Window #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_14">Graveyard Drop Window #2</string>
  <string name="HH_title_15">Specter Operator</string>
  <string name="HH_title_16">Graveyard Zombie #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_17">Graveyard Zombie #2</string>
  <string name="HH_title_18">Mausoleum #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_19">Mausoleum #2</string>
  <string name="HH_title_20">Mausoleum #3</string>
  <string name="HH_title_21">Mausoleum #4</string>
  <string name="HH_title_22">Voodoo Master</string>
  <string name="HH_title_23">Torso Boy</string>
  <string name="HH_title_24">Slaughterhouse #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_25">Slaughterhouse #2</string>
  <string name="HH_title_26">Hillbilly #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_27">Hillbilly #2</string>
  <string name="HH_title_28">Grandpa Shack</string>
  <string name="HH_title_29">Grinder Barn</string>
  <string name="HH_title_30">Corn Creature #1</string>
  <string name="HH_title_31">Corn Creature #2</string>
  
  <string name="HH_info_1">This is a 3 part job. While Pa gets the attation of the crowd you need 
      to bust out the door and run at your targets.\n
      You will need dialog on this part: \n
      You all look good enough to eat.\n
      Meals on wheels\n
      Be creative but be fast, Pa and your daughter have parts too.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_2">This is a 3 part job. Gain the attation of the crowd by using dialog.\n
      MA! FRESH MEAT!\n
      WHAT YOU ALL DOING HERE. MA FRESH MEAT\n
      Be creative on your dialog. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_3">This is a 3 part job. You are the last part, have your chainsaw pre-cranked 
      and ready to go. When Ma and Pa do their thing run out screaming and shouting. \n
      Use some dialog but be loud and creative.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_4">You press the button for the mp3 to start T-Rex sounds. Push down on the lever 
      to open the jaw of the T-Rex.\n
      Don\'t step out into the open. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_5">Hide in the woods and run up to the trailer. Scream and shout, as your become a distraction 
      for your partner. When one of you scares them the other needs to attack the other side. \n
      Use dialog on this and be creative, your goal is to be a sick murderer hunter in the woods.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_6">Hide in the woods and run up to the trailer. Scream and shout, as your become a distraction 
      for your partner. When one of you scares them the other needs to attack the other side. \n
      Use dialog on this and be creative, your goal is to be a sick murderer hunter in the woods.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_7">All the effects in the shed are automated. Wait until the trailer is around 
      the barrels then push them out. Run out screaming and shouting.  \n
      Use dialog like: \n
      TIME TO DIE\n
      YOU WANT TO DIE HERE\n
      Be creative with your dialog and actions. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_8">Work with your partner, as the targets are looking at the Serpent run out screaming and 
      shouting. While one attacks one side pause and attack the other side confusing your targets. \n
      Use creative dialog on this position. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_9">Work with your partner, as the targets are looking at the Serpent run out screaming and 
      shouting. While one attacks one side pause and attack the other side confusing your targets. \n
      Use creative dialog on this position.</string>
  
  <string name="HH_info_10">You or your partner need to activate the flames, then as the dragon attacks 
      work with your partner, as the targets are looking at the Serpent run out screaming and 
      shouting. While one attacks one side pause and attack the other side confusing your targets. \n
      Be creative on your dialog.\n
      WARNING: DO NOT ATTEMPT TO LIGHT THE FLAME BY ANY OTHER MEANS THEN WHAT YOUR ARE TOLD. DO NOT EDIT OR 
      TRY TO FIX THE FAME SETUP.\n
      DOING SO CAN CAUSE SERIOUS INJURY AND OR DEATH TO YOU AND OR OTHERS. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_11">You or your partner need to activate the flames, then as the dragon attacks 
      work with your partner, as the targets are looking at the Serpent run out screaming and 
      shouting. While one attacks one side pause and attack the other side confusing your targets. \n
      Be creative on your dialog.\n
      WARNING: DO NOT ATTEMPT TO LIGHT THE FLAME BY ANY OTHER MEANS THEN WHAT YOUR ARE TOLD. DO NOT EDIT OR 
      TRY TO FIX THE FAME SETUP.\n
      DOING SO CAN CAUSE SERIOUS INJURY AND OR DEATH TO YOU AND OR OTHERS.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_12">You are to welcome everyone to your home. You can act reserved or crazy as you wish. 
      Not much is known about this part far as acting because most people die on the first week.\n
      Use dialog such as: \n
      WECOME HOME, Final stop is 6 feet down.\n
      WATCH WHAT YOU ARE DOING OR YOU WILL END UP LIKE THE REST.\n
      Be creative in your dialog.
	  Yea we don\'t know what happened to the other guys.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_13">Work with your partner and attack at the same time. Click the lever and scream your targets.
      You will have a peek hole to see your targets. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_14">Work with your partner and attack at the same time. Click the lever and scream your targets.
      You will have a peek hole to see your targets.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_15">All the sound is automated. Push the rig out to attack with it. Do not step out into the open. 
      </string>
  <string name="HH_info_16">Slowly rise from the grave or run at them. No dialog will be needed just screams and shouts. 
      Make noises that will scare your targets and work with your partner to attack.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_17">Slowly rise from the grave or run at them. No dialog will be needed just screams and shouts. 
      Make noises that will scare your targets and work with your partner to attack.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_18">No dialog will be needed just screams and shouts. Run at your target and make noises that will 
      scare your targets and work with your partner to attack. If you are operating the drop windows wait until the trailer 
      is nearby and hang out trying to grab them. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_19">No dialog will be needed just screams and shouts. Run at your target and make noises that will 
      scare your targets and work with your partner to attack. If you are operating the drop windows wait until the trailer 
      is nearby and hang out trying to grab them.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_20">No dialog will be needed just screams and shouts. Run at your target and make noises that will 
      scare your targets and work with your partner to attack. If you are operating the drop windows wait until the trailer 
      is nearby and hang out trying to grab them.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_21">No dialog will be needed just screams and shouts. Run at your target and make noises that will 
      scare your targets and work with your partner to attack. If you are operating the drop windows wait until the trailer 
      is nearby and hang out trying to grab them.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_22">You will do a short chant and then attack by running at your targets. Activate the flames by the 
      switch on your right. \n
      Dialog is needed: \n
      I WILL MAKE YOU ALL BURN IN HELL!\n
      Be creative on your dialog.\n
      WARNING: DO NOT ATTEMPT TO LIGHT THE FLAME BY ANY OTHER MEANS THEN WHAT YOUR ARE TOLD. DO NOT EDIT OR 
      TRY TO FIX THE FAME SETUP.\n
      DOING SO CAN CAUSE SERIOUS INJURY AND OR DEATH TO YOU AND OR OTHERS.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_23">You need to stay still until the voodoo master is done. You will then scream and shout. \n
      Dialog is optional:\n
      HELP ME!\n
      WHERE IS MY BODY. AHHHH HELP ME.\n
      Be creative on the dialog.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_24">One guy will operate the lights and other one the door. When the lights go off bust out of the 
      sliding door and attack with CHAINSAWS!!!!! If music is available then time it well with the lights and the trailer entering 
      the house. Jump on the back of the trailer and get close but do not touch them with the chainsaws.\n
      Use dialog such as:\n 
      WANT TO GO FOR A RIDE BARBIE GIRL!\n
      YOU READY TO DIE TONIGHT.\n
      Be very creative, but loud so they can hear you. Work with your partner.\n
      I love this part, just kill them all.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_25">One guy will operate the lights and other one the door. When the lights go off bust out of the 
      sliding door and attack with CHAINSAWS!!!!! If music is available then time it well with the lights and the trailer entering 
      the house. Jump on the back of the trailer and get close but do not touch them with the chainsaws.\n
      Use dialog such as:\n 
      WANT TO GO FOR A RIDE BARBIE GIRL!\n
      YOU READY TO DIE TONIGHT.\n
      Be very creative, but loud so they can hear you. Work with your partner.\n
      I love this part, just kill them all.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_26">Your job is the mumble like a hillbilly and sound like one. Jump into the trailer and go all 
      hillbilly on them.\n
      Dialog will be needed: \n
      What you all doing here huh, grandpa going to kill you.\n
      Be creative and work with your partners and what is available at the time. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_27">Your job is the mumble like a hillbilly and sound like one. Jump into the trailer and go all 
      hillbilly on them.\n
      Dialog will be needed: \n
      What you all doing here huh, grandpa going to kill you.\n
      Be creative and work with your partners and what is available at the time. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_28">Your job is the mumble like a hillbilly and sound like one. Jump into the trailer and go all 
      hillbilly on them.\n
      Dialog will be needed: \n
      What you all doing here huh, grandpa going to kill you.\n
      Be creative and work with your partners and what is available at the time. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_29">Activate the grinders that will slam down on your victims and then act crazy. 
      Be creative on the dialog.</string>
  <string name="HH_info_30">Jump out of the corn and attack. There is no dialog just sound of anger and terror. </string>
  <string name="HH_info_31">Jump out of the corn and attack. There is no dialog just sound of anger and terror.</string>
  
  
  <string name="ZT_title_1">Street Zombie #1</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_2">Street Zombie #2</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_3">Street Zombie #3</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_4">Street Zombie #4</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_5">Street Zombie #5</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_6">Door Bust Zombie #1</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_7">Door Bust Zombie #2</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_8">Doctor</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_9">Doc room Zombie</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_10">Clinic Bed Zombie</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_11">Nurse with baby</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_12">Cage Zombie #1</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_13">Cage Zombie #2</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_14">Bus Zombie #1</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_15">Bus Zombie #2</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_16">Clinic Window Zombie</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_17">Street Zombie #6</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_18">Garage Zombie</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_19">Junk Yard Zombie #1</string>
  <string name="ZT_title_20">Junk Yard Zombie #2</string>

  <string name="ZT_info_1">You are the first line of defense. You need to be in the 
      flower shop ready for the first target. When your targets enter the town, wait until they hit the first turn 
      then step out or stumble out of the shop. Use sounds, monas, groans, and zombie 
      noises to make your targets feel at home. \n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_2">Work with the other street zombies to attack your target. Try to hide behind objects and/or 
      lay on the ground. When they get close stand up or craw to your targets making sounds and noises like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed. </string>
  <string name="ZT_info_3">Work with the other street zombies to attack your target. Try to hide behind objects and/or 
      lay on the ground. When they get close stand up or craw to your targets making sounds and noises like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_4">Work with the other street zombies to attack your target. Try to hide behind objects and/or 
      lay on the ground. When they get close stand up or craw to your targets making sounds and noises like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_5"> Hide in the truck and wait until they get close by, then reach out and attack them. Work 
      with the other street zombies to attack your target. Make sounds and noises like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_6">Work with your partner as your targets get close to the doors bust out reaching for them. 
      One of you can craw on the ground for added effect.\n
      No actual words will be needed. </string>
  <string name="ZT_info_7">Work with your partner as your targets get close to the doors bust out reaching for them. 
      One of you can craw on the ground for added effect.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_8">You will play a doctor that has gone mad. Try to say you have the cure, and get them into the room. 
      Set it up for your zombie partner to get your targets. This is a 2 person job. \n
      Use dialog like:\n
      IT\'S OK I HAVE THE CURE. IT IS RIGHT HERE IN THIS FRIDGE.\n
      COME IN COME IN THIS IS A SAFE ROOM.\n
      Depending on where your zombie is change your dialog.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_9">Work with your doc to get your targets. If you use the fridge get in and wait until he opens 
      the door. Attack your targets changing your actions as the night goes on. Sound walk and act like zombie. \n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_10">Lay on the bed as a dead body or craw under it. When your targets get close go nuts and attack. 
      Act and sound like a freshly reanimated corpse.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_11">You will carry a baby in your arms and walk around the cribs. When your targets enter the room 
      look at them with you rage and helpless ness then attack. \n
      Use words like:\n
      SAVE MY BABY!\n
      IT\'S MY BABY!\n
      Be creative with your dialog.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_12">Work with your partner as you bounce off the walls crazy trying to escape. Sound like a zombie 
      and bang against the cage.\n 
      No actual words will be needed. </string>
  <string name="ZT_info_13">Work with your partner as you bounce off the walls crazy trying to escape. Sound like a zombie 
      and bang against the cage.\n 
      No actual words will be needed. </string>
  <string name="ZT_info_14">Hide behind the seats and wait until your targets get close. Use sounds and actions like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed. </string>
  <string name="ZT_info_15">Hide behind the seats and wait until your targets get close. Use sounds and actions like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_16">Wait and bust of the window to attack as they pass by. Use sounds and actions like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_17">As they get off the bus and around the corner come out of the tattoo shop. Use sounds and actions 
      like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_18">As they come close to the front of the truck activate the flame and then deactivate it. Then jump out 
      attacking like a zombie. Use sounds and actions like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_19">Final push, work with your partner and scare your targets into the darkest part of boon hall. 
      Use sounds and actions like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed.</string>
  <string name="ZT_info_20">Final push, work with your partner and scare your targets into the darkest part of boon hall. 
      Use sounds and actions like a zombie.\n
      No actual words will be needed</string>
  
</resources>
